=Lady Liberty=
=Episode 5=
(Dingqi Reading Platform)
Mr. Fan.
Looking for Gu Yan?
I can only give you
the official response.
I can pass on a message for you.
But as for meeting in person...
Gu Yan isn't taking visitors right now.
Mr. Fan,
authors are supposed to come in
for a weekly briefing.
When is he coming in?
Can't I just get a glimpse of him
from a distance?
He was just here yesterday afternoon.
He won't be back
for another week.
We're setting up
a live chat
between Gu Yan and the readers soon.
I'll let you know
when the stream goes live, okay?
That flash drive has
all the archival photos
I found for the author.
It took me a month in the library
to put that together.
If I can't find it,
I'll have to start over again.
Could you check the elevator's
security footage from yesterday?
See if anyone picked it up.
Could you rewind
that part for me?
What about the flash drive?
That guy
looks like an old friend of mine.
Look, Miss.
You're looking for a flash drive.
I'm not showing the footage
so you could find your friends.
If you don't see it,
I'm turning this off.
Lin Zhanqiao...
This Gu Yan seems like a rookie.
Probably around twenty-four or five.
He's not among the authors I know.
(Executive Director's Office)
Also...
he and Lin Zhanqiao
showed up at Dingqi
around the same time.
If Chenxing doesn't have
a new ace up their sleeve,
why would they let He Han
and Hong Qigong go?
Mantou.
I'm meeting an author today.
I'm leaving early.
What about Hong Qigong?
She says she has a high fever
and brain fog.
She's on leave.
Tell her to get plenty of rest.
If she's not worried,
we're not worried.
We don't have
another top-tier author to replace her.
When the rankings come out,
it will look bad for us.
Begging her is worse.
I don't want this.
Krug Champagne is on promotion today.
It's an absolute steal.
Even Yi Shu wrote about it.
She said if she were rich,
she would spend all her money
on Krug Champagne.
It's just that popular.
(Year 2021)
- He Han!
Here's to us.
To us!
(Year 2023)
Cheers.
Congratulations, Ms. Lin.
Congratulations to you, superstar.
Any other recommendations?
Yes.
We have another champagne here.
But the price
is about the same as the Krug
with today's discount.
Do you...
Thanks for the recommendation.
I'll take this one.
Alright.
I'll bag it for you.
Hello?
Ms. Lin?
I'm your neighbor.
Your mother is at your door.
She passed out from hunger.
I'm on my way. Thank you.
Ms. Lin.
Your mom has been waiting
at your door since this afternoon.
The old lady can't handle that.
I'm fine.
She's busy with work.
It's normal for me to wait.
Next time, I'll just bring some candy
or cookies with me.
Thank you so much.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Open the door.
I'm so sorry, Madam.
Thanks for taking care of her.
It was a miscommunication on our part.
You're so busy,
and neglecting your own mother?
Good thing I saw her today.
If I hadn't,
low blood sugar could be fatal.
- It's not that serious.
- You know what I mean.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Come on in.
I'm sorry.
I interrupted your work.
You still had things to do, right?
Why don't you go ahead and finish up?
I'll just...
I'll wait for you here.
Didn't I tell you on the phone
that I'd be working really late today?
I told you not to wait for me,
that you could come another day.
I got these vegetables and meat.
It's your father's birthday on Monday,
so I had to get the food ready anyway.
They wouldn't fit in my fridge,
so I brought them over
and put them in yours.
I could make
a couple of dishes for you, too.
So you'd have food after work.
You could've just
bought these groceries on Monday.
You can get this stuff
at the supermarket anytime.
Plus,
I barely ever cook at home.
I rarely eat here anyway,
so no need to cook for me.
What if you get hungry at night?
Takeout isn't as healthy
as a home-cooked meal.
Okay, I get it.
I won't do it next time.
Go ahead and do your thing.
Don't worry about me.
I'll leave as soon as I'm done.
Let me put
those flowers in a vase for you.
No, that's okay.
I bought them for a friend.
Hello, Ms. Lin.
I won't be coming to see you today.
Something came up at home.
We'll talk tomorrow.
Also,
send me the updated draft
as soon as it's done.
Okay, got it.
Have you had dinner?
I already ate.
Have some fruit, then.
No, I'm good.
(My parents)
(are gentle, kind people.)
(We truly care for)
(and love each other.)
(But we still struggle)
(to find a comfortable level of intimacy)
(that works for us.)
(Do picture-perfect families)
(actually exist?)
(Or are there always)
(hidden flaws?)
(Colorful Culture Media)
Why haven't you left yet?
You were handling matters
outside all by yourself.
It'd be unconscionable
for me to just leave.
Even though you act like a jerk
most of the time,
your diligence
is your one redeeming quality at work.
You can talk business with me only.
I'm much better at business
than relationships.
That's no fun.
I'm starving.
Are you sure Gu Yan
isn't with Dingqi?
Positive.
If he works for Lin Zhanqiao,
we won't be getting
Zhiyuan's money.
You could always go back.
Just tell Lin Zhanqiao
you were blinded by love.
But you've calmed down and are ready
to be with her.
If you're short on cash, I have some.
We're in the same boat.
Never mind.
I don't work for you.
I want this to be our company.
Only beer today.
But trust me.
Once the company takes off,
and I'm doing better,
I'll buy some good wine
and have a nice drink.
I know this sudden romance
isn't for me.
It's for Gu Yan.
But I'm still happy.
At least, you know
I'm useful to you.
That's why
you spend time trying to please me.
Right?
Come on.
Zhao Lanxin.
I'm single.
If you need a fake boyfriend
to start a company,
take photos, post online,
and stroke your ego,
that's fine.
But in private,
drop the act.
I have no interest in dating.
If there's no profit in it,
I won't please anyone.
Not even women.
All relationships are transactional.
On that point,
we agree.
I've got writer's block.
If the female lead gets humiliated
by the salon manager,
what should the male lead do?
The salon is full of women.
He can't just beat someone up
like at the hot pot place.
Just have him buy
the salon.
Fire the manager
and make her the boss.
If she's the boss,
the latter plot
will be too hard for her.
She's too pure and kind.
The staff would also bully her.
Then, have the male lead
interview the staff himself.
Reject the smart ones.
Only keep those purer than her.
It doesn't matter if it runs well.
As long as she's happy.
And she still won't marry him?
Not yet.
She'll agree at the end.
Plus, the male lead
isn't the type to force marriage.
He'll wait until she's ready
and willing before he asks.
Is that what you think too?
Are you waiting
for my "I do"?
I'm not.
Definitely not.
I am the type
to force marriage.
So if I haven't asked,
I haven't thought about it.
Go update your chapter.
Be good.
So you're staying up
to wait for my update?
Yes, that's the case.
I'll get to it.
Wait for me.
(Gu Yan's "Drunk Old Friend" updated.)
(Drunk Old Friend)
(Start Reading)
(Chapter 63: The Dance Mystery III)
Don't fall asleep.
I'm updating soon.
Another 20 minutes.
It'll be ready.
(Select Tip Amount)
I'm leaving.
Take care of yourself.
Don't work too hard.
There's food in the fridge.
Bring it to your dad soon.
(For Lin)
(For Monday morning,
expiring Tuesday afternoon.)
Tomorrow at 10:30 AM,
Gu Yan will have a livestream
on Dingqi Reading Platform.
I'll go early
to try to chat with him.
You won't get a chance there.
Better to print out our terms
and offers for him
to read.
They're all ready.
So our priorities are...
First, Gu Yan.
Second, Hong Qigong.
Third, Zhugan Dalang.
We'll start with Lin Zhanqiao,
and poach the talented rookies
her editors are managing.
The rookies?
I already told them
we're changing our terms.
No more monthly salaries.
Bonuses based on click tiers.
A lot of them
will struggle to live.
That just proves
they aren't meant for this.
Why didn't you discuss this with me?
If you land Gu Yan,
would you even care
how I deal with the rookies?
You being so anxious now
just proves that you can't
land him.
It's "us."
This isn't just on me.
Startups are hard.
Survival of the fittest.
If you can't deliver,
I'll have to consider other partners.
I'll walk you back.
No need.
I'm staying at my place today.
It's across the street.
I'll walk you over.
Okay.
I've always wanted to ask,
why do you stay at Lin Zhanqiao's place
instead of your own?
Is her place closer to work?
No.
Traffic from her place is terrible.
Then, are you afraid
of being alone?
Nope.
You don't seem afraid of being alone.
It's my mom's judgment.
She's a neat freak.
Every time before she comes over,
I have to clean up.
But it never meets her standards.
So then I figured,
if someone lives there,
it'll never be spotless.
So I just don't stay there.
It's now a showroom.
♪First time in love♪
♪It tears my heart apart♪
♪Keep chasing on♪
♪Yet no one will ever know♪
♪For long time♪
♪Hope to lean on your side♪
♪And here you are♪
♪Calling my name in the air♪
♪Stay with open arms♪
(Bestseller List)
(Amnesia: My Bossy,
Love-Obsessed Husband)
Mimi's Love-Obsessed Husband
hit number one on the women's chart.
That's great news.
We should celebrate.
("Completely hooked and can't stop")
(is popping up all over the comments.)
(Dingqi Livestream)
(Based on the current data,)
(Drunk Old Friend
is gaining serious momentum.)
I've never seen you
care so much about a rookie.
I'm verifying your theory.
What theory?
That Gu Yan
is Lin Zhanqiao's secret weapon.
(Online Fan Meet: Drunk Old Friend)
(Hit Author: Gu Yan)
Today, we are honored to invite
the author himself, Gu Yan,
and his talent scout editor
to our livestream
to meet everyone.
Let Mr. Fan know
Gu Yan is here.
Lin Zhanqiao?
Gu Yan?
My author.
Mr. Fan.
Zhanqiao.
We can finally
announce our collaboration.
Young man.
Your new update yesterday
set another click record.
It's very promising.
Let's go.
Come.
Have a seat inside.
Alright, book lovers,
you can see who has joined
our livestream today.
We have the author himself, Gu Yan,
and our star editor, Ms. Zhanqiao.
(Welcome to both of you.)
(So, Gu Yan, could you briefly)
(introduce your background?)
Gu Yan, may I ask
what Zhanqiao whispered to you?
She...
She just told me
to tell the truth.
It was pretty cool.
(As we all know,)
(talent is common,
but a good scout is rare.)
(Ms. Lin has a sharp eye)
(and exceptional abilities.)
You've grown, Lin Zhanqiao.
Are you jealous?
Why would I be?
I'm happy for her.
She finally found a good card to play.
Lin Zhanqiao has been holding
this card for a long time.
At least
half a year.
Why are you looking at me?
Now it seems
this card is being used against
Zhao Lanxin and Ling Yikai.
But initially, it must have been
to replace you.
No surprise.
I'm not exactly
a cooperative author.
She's wanted to replace me for a while.
Of course,
Gu Yan could never replace me.
And Lin Zhanqiao
doesn't have any confidence in him.
Or she would've released this sooner.
When Zhao Lanxin challenged her,
she forced him into the spotlight.
When did you find Gu Yan?
It's been a while.
I've never seen a contract for him.
I haven't signed the contract yet.
Why not?
Guarding against us?
You couldn't have known
Ling Yikai and I were leaving.
I'm not that clairvoyant.
But after so long,
I know the kind of person
Ling Yikai is.
He worked so hard
to secure the Zhiyuan Investment,
and kept me completely out of the loop.
I had a feeling
he'd negotiate with me.
I was guarding against him.
I didn't know
you'd leave.
Keeping it from me
is guarding against me.
Do you really think
Gu Yan can surpass He Han?
It's up to him.
At least he's surpassed Hong Qigong.
Did you watch Gu Yan's livestream?
Congratulations, Ms. Lin.
Nice trick, keeping him hidden.
But I'm a bit busy right now.
I'm just heading out
to celebrate Mimi hitting number one.
(Honestly, Drunk Old Friend)
(wouldn't be where it is today)
(without my editor,)
(also my boss, Ms. Lin.)
Before I met her,
I opened an internet cafe with a friend.
I worked the night shift every night.
When it got busy,
(Mengtong Internet Cafe, Year 2023)
the new computers were taken.
I could only
use the old ones to read web novels.
After reading so many,
I started writing my own.
Ms. Lin discovered me.
There was a line I wrote
in Drunk Old Friend.
"Drunk, I miss the vast misty waters.
Waking, my old friend's tea is still warm."
This inscription in Drunk Old Friend
was written for Lin Zhanqiao.
I could even say
that the entirety of Drunk Old Friend
was written for Lin Zhanqiao.
Just like how books always had
"Dedicated to so-and-so"
on the title page.
It's the same idea.
Before I met Lin Zhanqiao,
I was just
a night-shift internet cafe admin.
In a basement,
wearing headphones, smoking, swearing,
and eating instant noodles.
Writing novels was just an outlet.
Like daydreaming.
(Annihilation Secret)
Dreaming of getting rich.
(The Return of the Phantom Knight)
Dreaming of moving up.
Dreaming of being a hero.
I wouldn't even call them dreams.
At best,
they were delusions.
Until Lin Zhanqiao found me.
When I saw her,
I felt like
I had known her for a long time.
Or rather,
I felt like
I was meant to wait here
for someone like her.
To pick
a piece of trash like me
out of the dumpster.
To give me validation and support
without disgust.
In my whole life,
no one has ever
given me so much patience and time.
If you like the story
you are reading now,
it's not because of Gu Yan.
It's because of Lin Zhanqiao.
All the praise and honors I receive
in my past, present,
and future,
should first belong to Lin Zhanqiao.
She taught me,
and encouraged me.
That's the only reason
you are able to read
these chapters today.
This place is nice.
Of course.
It's quite lively here.
Let's sit there.
Okay.
Hello, Mr. He.
I'm Zhangzhu,
Ms. Lin's assistant at Chenxing.
We met yesterday, right?
Remember me?
The number one fan.
Yes, your fan.
Hello, I'm Mimi.
I'm He Han's girlfriend.
Meeting a Love-Obsessed Husband.
Congratulations
on hitting number one today.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Where's your boss?
Livestreaming with Gu Yan.
They'll be here.
I came ahead to order.
What a coincidence.
Let's sit together, then.
Together...
Sit here?
This...
Is it inconvenient?
What a coincidence.
Ms. Lin.
Mr. He is here
to celebrate
his girlfriend's top ranking.
Let me introduce you.
Gu Yan.
He Han.
Zhangzhu.
Mimi.
Hello, Mr. He.
Don't call me Mr. He.
Call me senior.
After all, our mutual mentor
is Ms. Lin Zhanqiao.
And let me tell you,
I gave you this month
so you could seize the opportunity
to have a head start.
Because Ms. Lin has been
having a run of bad luck lately.
She can only rely on you
to boost her career.
I'll do my best.
But you're the ceiling in this industry.
I'll learn from you.
Don't stress yourself out.
After all, I met He Han when he was
in his early twenties.
He wasn't even as good as you now.
Of course.
I was only twenty myself back then.
As an editor,
my experience
wasn't what it is now.
Completely incompetent.
Ms. Lin, should we
move to another table?
Because it seems
He Han wants to sit here.
I'm afraid it might be
inconvenient when we talk business.
No need.
We'll leave. You guys chat here.
Come, sit down.
Sit.
Enjoy.
Excuse me. Please bring out our cake.
Thank you.
I need to record this.
I want to film the finger heart.
Yeah, like so.
Put it together with mine.
Yay!
I, Mimi, have reached the top!
The top!
I want to eat that.
Want to join them, Zhangzhu?
No.
I just didn't expect He Han to be so...
Cheesy?
No, just different from what I imagined.
I didn't expect you to be so young.
How old are you?
Twenty-six.
I'm twenty-two.
Okay.
You don't seem to talk much.
Why do your characters
talk so much?
Isn't it true that authors
give their protagonists
whatever they lack themselves?
Wish fulfillment.
Lean back.
I'll lean back too.
I'll do it too.
So, do you read He Han's novels?
I have.
What do you think?
I feel like
I'm the better writer.
In a month,
I might surpass him.
I admire your spirit.
No one has ever dared
to challenge He Han before.
Good luck.
What?
You went into my bedroom?
I didn't go in there on purpose.
I just couldn't find my stuff,
so I went in to look.
That's still not okay.
But there's no one else in your room,
and you have nothing to hide.
Why do you care so much?
It's not about what's in my bedroom.
It's about you breaking our agreement.
Fine, I was wrong.
I won't do it again, okay?
There is no "again."
Do you not love me anymore?
I don't.
You said you loved me.
That you'd make me
incredibly successful.
You've reached the top.
Isn't that enough?
But you said
you loved me the most.
And that you were going to marry me.
You said you'd accept
all my flaws.
I absolutely did not.
That's what the male lead
in your novel said.
Not me.
The male lead is you!
And I'm the female lead!
You decided that on your own.
What do you mean?
I think
we should break up.
He Han...
He Han!
Why would you dump me
right at my peak?
Wouldn't it be worse
to dump you at your lowest?
Oh my god. That's so humiliating.
Don't worry. He's fine.
He's used to it.
You think that's fine?
It might bother someone else, but
he's probably enjoying it.
Looks like my luck is bad too.
Sorry about that.
Did I scare you?
We're having a work meeting here.
It's not a good time.
That's okay. I don't mind.
What was my junior's pen name again?
Return of the Phantom Knight?
The Phantom Knight
stopped writing ages ago.
How did he return?
Just paying tribute.
Even though his writing
falls far short compared to the original
Phantom Knight,
it still has its moments.
I've heard of the Phantom Knight.
He can be considered
the founding father of online fiction.
But later on,
he suddenly stopped writing.
Back then,
online authors didn't use real names.
So no one knows who he really is.
I just figured
that borrowing his name
wouldn't cause any trouble.
Mr. He, Ms. Lin.
You're experienced.
Have you ever met Phantom Knight?
- No.
If he came back,
all of us could stop writing.
Seriously.
We'd be sent packing.
That was over a decade ago.
If he really came back,
I could still win.
Just focus on getting over
the hill in front of you first.
Alright.
Take your time.
I'm taking off.
Only twenty days left
until the deadline.
Keep at it, Junior.
Make our mentor proud.
Well?
Did the idol's true color
hurt you?
Don't you think he's super cute?
(Hello, everyone, I'm Mimi!)
(Today is a day of double blessings.)
(The first is that)
(Fans lining up)
("Love-Obsessed Husband" has reached)
(Number one fan is here)
(the top of the women's chart!)
(Thank you all for your love.)
(And thank you
for your ongoing support.)
(I will continue to write)
(many more great stories.)
(Please look forward to them.)
(I love you guys!)
(Who is this?)
(The second is that)
(A new work?)
(I finally saw him for who he truly is)
(What are we talking about?)
(and I dumped him!)
Do you think it's worth it for He Han?
He helped her succeed
only to get publicly trashed.
Mimi leaves,
and another Lily
or Niuniu will take her place.
They know the deal.
As long as they date him,
their novels will shoot up the charts.
Plenty are willing.
But honestly,
if he dates
only one girlfriend for a while,
breaks up, and then dates the next,
it's fine.
And he genuinely
helps each girlfriend get on the charts.
In a sense,
that makes him a high-quality boyfriend.
He met Gu Yan today.
Was it tense?
He's jealous of Gu Yan.
I could tell.
Tell the truth,
is Gu Yan your little boyfriend?
No.
It's just an author-editor relationship.
An author and editor
can be boyfriend and girlfriend too.
It's better not to be.
Do you regret breaking up
with He Han?
Regret what?
If we hadn't broken up,
Gu Yan wouldn't have been
forced into the spotlight,
and wouldn't be
an overnight success now.
I didn't mean professionally.
You mean his character?
Just two words.
Selfish.
Narcissistic.
He Han still loves you.
At least, I think he still does.
He said
he loves me.
But everyone
expresses love differently.
He says he loves me.
But he can't share his life with me
long-term and stably.
He writes so many novels,
and he really thinks he's trapped in
some tragic past life memory
that he can't reveal.
That he has to stay away
from the mortal world
and worldly love.
Otherwise,
he'll drag
everyone around him down to ashes,
or even send them
to eternal damnation.
But stories like that
only fool young girls.
I have produced
hundreds of stories like that.
I don't buy it.
Please give this to Lawyer Bei.
It's Chenxing's contract with Gu Yan.
I want the terms to be more binding.
Why?
Don't you trust him?
He seems like an honest young man.
That's because
he hasn't met enough people,
and temptations yet.
But, you know,
people change.
(Questionnaire)
Are you done?
There are hundreds of questions.
And you paid a thousand yuan for them?
I could have
taken you to a bar
for five hundred yuan.
This does precision matching.
The guys you meet at bars
are just lonely and looking for
a good time.
So you spend a thousand,
and that guarantees
they want a serious relationship?
He Han spent more on you.
It's different.
This ensures our values align.
Look at this question.
"Do you think that love
requires being together day and night?"
My answer is definitely yes.
In "The Return of the Condor Heroes",
a husband
is only a husband
if he's within arm's reach.
So the system
will definitely match me
with someone who answered
similarly to me on this question.
Someone like He Han
would obviously never enter my system.
There was a performance art piece.
A woman tied herself to her boyfriend
for a month.
Then, they never
spoke to each other again.
We don't have to be tied together.
At the very least,
he shouldn't ban me from his bedroom.
I need to pray
to my almighty toothbrush.
Clear the clouds.
Bring me true love.
After you finish the test,
how soon do they deliver your true love?
One business day
for the review results.
♪Died a little inside last night♪
♪Cause I'll never see you again♪
♪I'm waking up to silence around me♪
♪Heal, can I heal?♪
♪All I want is nothing more♪
(Please update, He Han! I'm begging you!
A month is just way too long!)
(Why pause updates for a month?)
♪I don't wanna leave the memories♪
(Zhangzhu: Gu Yan is no threat.
He Han is the GOAT.)
♪The way to forget you♪
♪Never forget you♪
(Colorful Culture Media)
Wu Jian called.
Zhiyuan decided to invest
in Chenxing.
They are making a bigger splash.
Do you know how much this office
costs a month?
What are you getting at?
Bringing in a new partner
would relieve
the pressure on us.
A female partner?
She brings in
well-known traditional authors,
and a ten-million investment.
Isn't that good?
What's her name?
Qiao Qiao.
Her?
I disagree.
Find me a ten-million investment,
and then you get to disagree.
(Qiao Qiao, Publisher & Author)
There are many authors
with good attitudes,
but a top-ranked author
as helpful as you?
You're the first.
Per your requirements,
I've made detailed provisions.
You don't even need to be present.
I can negotiate with him privately.
Have you looked over these contracts?
I've seen them.
If you've seen them, I'll just sign.
(If what He Han troubled me with)
(was an unplaceable lightness,)
(what Gu Yan is forcing on me now)
(is an unbearable weight.)
(I've been thinking.)
(Everyone's most comfortable level of intimacy)
(is probably different.)
♪If the sky♪
♪And the sea♪
♪Turned upside down♪
♪If a swimming fish♪
♪Fell in love with a flying bird♪
♪If back then♪
♪We had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪So let this surging love♪
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain♪
♪That's alright♪
♪If we're buried♪
♪By passing years all the better♪
♪At least we still can keep♪
♪This one eternal photograph♪
♪We're on misaligned tracks♪
♪Running in opposite ways♪
♪Searching all along the way♪
♪For the fire of our younger hearts♪
♪And the beauty lost in time♪
♪This time don't lose each other again♪
♪Only after loss♪
♪Do we learn what truly matters most♪
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll stay and walk together♪
♪Till we grow old♪
♪But still the sky will never♪
♪Turn with the sea♪
♪But still a swimming fish won't♪
♪Fall in love with a flying bird♪